亲爱的  过来看看这个
Honey, you got to come see this.
九个月之前
我要走了
I'm going to go.
带瓦奥莱特去娇家
I'm taking Violet and going to Jo's.
去弗罗里达
Florida?
我想赶在新学年开始前到那
I want to get there before the school year starts.
我不明白
I don't understand.
那去洛杉矶的计划呢
What about Los Angeles?
我们不是说好在那开始新生活吗
I thought we agreed about the fresh start.
我做不到
I just can't.
-我们努力过了  -我们还没努力呢
- We really tried. - We haven't tried.
我忍受不了了
I can't do it anymore.
那是治疗  不是努力
Therapy isn't trying.
那只是让你把这些事想明白
It's just figuring stuff out
这样你就能真的努力去做些什么
so you can really do something.
我努力了
I've tried,
我越努力想让你重新
and as much as I keep trying
走入我的生活  我心里的坎就越宽
to let you in again, this wall comes up,
我真的跨不过这坎
and I... I can't... I can't get past it.
看看这所房子
Just look at this house.
看看我找到的这所房子  在汉考克公园附近
Look at this house I found. It's right near
周围有很多二十年代的豪宅
Hancock Park, where all those big mansions from the '20s are.
你总说很想要一幢这样的房子
You always talked about how much you wanted a house like this--
这种很有个性的房子
one with personality.
这幢就是
Well, here it is.
你还是不明白
You don't listen.
一幢房子解决不了问题  本
The house isn't going to fix it, Ben.
这只是幢房子 小维  答应吧
It's just a house, Viv. Come on.
看一看
Take a look.
它很棒  对吗
It's nice, right?
蒂凡尼的灯饰  还有其他豪华装饰
Tiffany lamps and everything.
我不明白  可能它闹鬼还是怎么的
I don't know, maybe it's haunted or something.
价钱还没定死
I mean, it's still a stretch at that price,
而且它已经挂牌很久还没卖出去
but it's been on the market for a while,
所以价钱可能还会更低
so maybe they'll go lower.
还有间办公室
There's even an office,
这样我就能在家见病人
so I can see patients at home.
它真的很完美
I mean, it's perfect.
不行
No.
亲爱的  你之所以不喜欢
Honey... honey, the reason
我的搬家建议是因为
you can't hold on to this idea of leaving
你不想这样做
is because it's not what you want.
我已经找了一个月房子了
I-I've been looking at houses for a month,
当我看到这所房子时  我发誓
and when I found this one, I swear to God,
就像...就像是
it was like a... it was like a laser beam
醍醐灌顶一样
shot right into my brain.
我能看见咱们以后在那生活的样子
I could see it all so clearly.
就像是过电影一样
It was like a movie in my mind.
咱们全家在一起  你  我还有瓦奥莱特
We were together-- you, me and Violet--
围在壁炉边
all around the fire.
瓦奥莱特在看那些忧郁的俄国小说
Violet was reading some depressing Russian novel,
我在生火
and I was stoking the fire,
你在沙发上哄孩子睡觉
and you were on the couch rocking a baby.
亲爱的  我们以前凭感觉就
Honey... we have made so many life choices
做了很多人生决定  而现在
based on our gut, and right now...
我的感觉告诉我这地方...
my gut is telling me that this place...
这房子会...
this house is going to...
它会让你迈过你心里的那道坎
it's going to break down that wall inside you.
我相信那是所漂亮的房子
I'm sure it's a beautiful house.
我真的非常爱你
I love you so much.
我求你了
I'm begging you...
去看看这房子吧
just come see the house.
我们三个飞过去
The three of us will fly out.
看看这房子
Just come see it.
当我第一次
When I look at this place,
看见这房子时  我感觉
for the first time, I feel...
它似乎充满着希望
like there's hope.
维维安
Vivien?
Vivien!
瓦奥莱特
Violet!
维维安
Vivien!
你在哪呢  维维安
Where are you, Vivien?
维维安
Vivien!
你在哪啊
Where are you?
■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：AlbotScorpy Asianika控女佣 小樱爱V妈 Tate只爱小鸟一个
翻译：艾丝爱康丝  泰特么二  苍木  威廉  费列罗西瓜
■
时间轴:Godwuwen  小萌要推到搁浅 后期制作: loved
校对:佩顿和Tate相爱了 小独 草草 妖月Tateraphim总监: 豆丁
我们以为你明天
We weren't expecting you until tomorrow,
-葬礼后才过来呢  -我知道
- after the service. - I know.
但我不能这么麻烦你  康丝坦斯
But I can't impose on you like this, Constance.
别傻了
Don't be silly.
照看这个小天使
Looking after this little angel
可一点都不麻烦
is no imposition whatsoever.
而且我真的不想
And I wouldn't think of burdening you
让你在经历过
with the care of a newborn
那些无可名状的悲剧之后
during this time of your...
就马上担起照看婴儿的责任
unspeakable tragedy.
谢谢  但...
Thank you, but...
维维安的妹妹已经过来了  所以...
Vivien's sister is here now, so...
明白了
Oh, I see.
远亲雪中送炭
What a blessing
是多么温馨啊
distant relations are in times of trouble.
麻烦你把他的东西都交给我吧
If I could just get his things...
当然
Certainly, uh...
但他马上就该吃午饭了
though it is nearly his lunchtime.
让我先把他喂饱
I know-- why don't I feed him?
他就会马上睡着  之后你就可以过来
He'll fall right asleep, and then you can come back
-你可以过几个小时再来  -我可以喂他
- in several hours. - I can feed him.
根本一点都不麻烦
It's really no trouble at all.
我是来接我儿子的  康丝坦斯
I'm here to get my son, Constance.
你儿子  当然了
Your son-- of course.
让我把他的东西收拾一下
Let me just gather up his things.
配方奶要加热了才能喂
This formula has to be warmed up.
你只需在热水管下冲一冲就好
All you have to do is run it under the hot water tap.
我会没事的
I'll be fine.
不  我想你会有事的
No, I don't believe you will.
你要是把孩子带回那房子  他也会出事的
Nor will that child if you take him back into that house.
-把他的东西给我  -哈蒙医生  听我一句
- Just give me his things. - Dr. Harmon, hear me.
那所房子有着可怕的力量
There are forces in that house
他们想要伤害孩子
that mean to do this child grave harm.
你我都心知肚明
We both know that it's true.
就是那力量杀死了你亲爱的妻子
The same forces that killed your sweet wife.
还有你的女儿呢
Oh, and what about your daughter?
告诉我  哈蒙医生
Tell me, Dr. Harmon,
你也给瓦奥莱特预备了口棺材吗
did you buy a casket for Violet, too?
如果那房子可以囚禁她的灵魂
If that house can claim her spirit,
它又会对这小宝宝做出什么事情呢
what's going to happen to this sweet little baby?
-孩子不会有事的  -你就是个傻瓜
- The baby's going to be fine. - Oh, you are a fool!
你看到了那么多事
After everything that you've seen...
发生了那么多事
after everything that has happened,
你怎么还这么有眼无珠
how can you still be so blind?
-你好  -我是本·哈蒙  泰特的治疗师
- Hello? - Hey, it's Ben Harmon, Tate's therapist.
我打这个电话是想说  我不能再治疗你的儿子了
Yeah, I'm calling because I can't treat your son anymore.
我可以给你另一个精神病医生的电话
I'd like to give you the number of another psychiatrist
我觉得这个医生可以帮到他
who I think could help him.
不是吧  为什么呢  医生
Oh, no, but why, Doctor?
因为你儿子和我女儿交往超越了我的底线
Because your son has crossed a line with my daughter.
可是...
Oh, but...
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
他现在在哪
Where is he?
在他的坟墓里
In his grave.
他在那里度过的时光远比活在世上的要长
Where he's been longer than he lived on this Earth.
你毁了我全家
You destroyed my family.
都是你
You!
你在为自己的罪孽还债  哈蒙医生
You are paying for your own sins, Dr. Harmon.
让我来给你一些建议吧
Let me give you some advice.
在我离开之后
When I leave here,
锁好你的门
lock your door
并且祈祷我不会回来找你算账
and pray I don't come back.
你适应的怎么样了
I wonder, how is your adjustment going?
我必须说  最难的事情
I have to say one of the hardest things
就是看着本
is watching Ben.
他都崩溃了
He's so devastated.
是啊  总是活人让我们难过
Yes, well, it's always the living that make it hard.
亲爱的  你并不用躲开
You don't need to run off, dear.
除非是你想  他是看不见你的
He can't see you unless you want him to.
对啊  总是记不住
Right. Keep forgetting.
我好想亲自照顾他啊
I want to nurse him so badly.
不要啊  本
No, Ben.
别用微波炉加热
Not the microwave.
你这叫阴魂不散  亲爱的
You're hovering, dear.
这样不好
It's a bad idea.
瞧  他还记得怎么做
See, he remembered.
他是个好爸爸
He was a good dad.
莫伊拉  我知道你不认同
Moira, I know you don't approve,
但是撇去他的那些缺点
but despite all his flaws...
他真的是个好父亲
he's a good father.
我真不明白你为什么总替他说话
I'll never understand why you always need to come to his defense.
来喝吧
Here you go.
你是想让他看见你吗  是这么回事吗
Do you want him to see you? Is that what's going on?
你在纠结要不要现身吗
Are you fighting the desire to appear?
不  我不想让他看见我
No, I do not want him to see me.
我绝对不想让他看见我或瓦奥莱特
I absolutely do not want him to see me or Violet.
我让她跟我保证过
I have made her promise me,
因为如果他看见了我们
because if he see us,
他就会想要留下了
then he is going to want to stay here.
-没事了  小家伙  -而他必须离开这栋房子
- It's okay, kiddo. - And he has to leave this house.
把我们的孩子抚养长大
And raise our baby.
那就乖乖坐下  保持距离
Then sit down and keep your distance.
记着一时软会千古恨
Remember the endgame.
一切都会没事的
It's all going to work out.
本身上有与众不同的地方
There's something about Ben that's different.
他总那么乐观
He's so sanguine.
或许他心里想着他能上手的女人
Perhaps he's dreaming of all the women he can have relations with.
原谅我
Forgive me.
这话不太中听
I suppose that was unkind.
莫伊拉  你能不能帮我泡杯茶
Moira, would you make me a cup of tea, please?
不
No.
你真是出奇的不肯接受现实
Your denial is impressive.
你现在是个鬼魂  哈蒙太太
You're a ghost, Mrs. Harmon.
我不受鬼魂的指使
I don't take orders from ghosts.
在这个世界里  你我是平等的
I'm your equal now in this world.
确实是
So you are.
我向你道歉
I owe you an apology.
我想你应该叫我维维安
And I think you should call me Vivien.
我会的
I'd like that.
维维安  我想说一句
Vivien, if I may...
让他去吧
Leave him be.
别折磨你自己
Don't torture yourself.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault.
你没有错
None of this is.
你娇姨妈很快就到了
Your Aunt Jo's going to be here soon.
好了
Okay.
乖乖
Okay. Okay.
没事了
It's okay.
-你不能这么做  -维维安
- You can't do this. - Vivien.
我就知道你在这里
I knew you were here.
为什么不出来见我
Why didn't you come to me?
因为这只会让事情变得更糟
It would just make it worse.
我想让你带着孩子离开这里
I want you to take the baby and go.
让我死  这样我们就能在一起了
No, just let me do it, then we can be together.
不  不行
No, no, no! No.
那孩子需要父亲  本
That baby needs a father, Ben.
我不是他的父亲
I'm not his father.
你我都心知肚明
You know it, and I know it.
他是我的孩子
He's my baby,
而且你现在不该抽烟
and you shouldn't be smoking.
我不管孩子的生父是谁
I don't really care where it came from.
要能照顾他  我愿倾尽所有
I would give anything if I could take care of him.
维维安  我对...
Vivien, I am...
让你遭受的这一切感到非常抱歉
so sorry for everything I put you through.
你听我说
I want you to hear me.
我原谅你了
I forgive you.
我们
So enough
经历了太多悲惨遭遇
with the drama and the tragedy.
这个家已经承受够多了
We've had enough in this family.
已经够了
We've had enough.
现在仅剩的唯一一丝光明
And the one spot of light
就是在楼上熟睡的孩子
that there is, is that baby asleep upstairs.
是时候该你做些壮举了
That's your opportunity to do something different.
我想让你抚养这个孩子
I want you to take the baby,
想让你离开这座房子
and I want you to leave this house,
再也不要回来
and I want you to never come back.
你妹妹说她会照顾他的
Your sister said she would take care of him.
她是个好母亲
She's a good mother.
不  我不想这样做
No, I don't want that.
那你想怎样
What do you want?
我想让你...
I want to...
抱着这个孩子  让他靠在你肩上
envision you with that boy on your shoulders
一起走在纽伯里的街上
walking down Newbury Street.
瓦奥莱特怎么办
What about Violet?
什么叫"瓦奥莱特怎么办"
我都已经十几岁了
I'm a teenage girl.
又不是姗姗学步的婴儿
Not exactly a cakewalk.
瓦奥莱特
Violet.
我到底是怎样的父亲
What kind of father have I been?
你三餐不食  不去学校
You weren't eating. You weren't going to school.
你已经过世了  而我却没发觉
You were already gone, and... I didn't get it.
是我将你拒之门外的
I shut you out.
我怕这事会让你崩溃
I was afraid it would break you.
我很想念你
I miss you so much.
我再也上不了哈佛了
I was never getting into Harvard.
但我可为你省下一大笔钱啊
But I saved you a shitload of money.
没错
Yeah, you did.
你得离开这里  爸爸
You have to leave, Dad.
你在这房子多待一分
Every minute you're in this house,
就会危险一分  那个孩子也一样
you're in danger, and so is that baby.
求你了
Please.
就当为了我们
Do it for us.
你要去哪里  本
Where are you going, Ben?
你觉得我会就这么让你走吗
You didn't think I'd just let you leave?
别挡路  海登
Get out of my way, Hayden.
我没时间听你废话
I don't have time for your bullshit.
现在我们可有的是时间了
Now we have all the time in the world.
欢迎  你们一定是雷默斯夫妇吧
Welcome! You must be the Ramos.
是的  我叫史黛西
Yes. I'm Stacy.
这是我丈夫米盖尔
This is my husband Miguel.
-你好  -米盖尔
- Hi. - Miguel.
很异域的名字啊  不得不说
What an exotic name. I must confess to a fascination
我对国境之南的一切都异常着迷
for all things south of the border.
实际上  我们来自西班牙
Actually, my family's from Spain.
再好不过了
All the better.
我觉得欧洲西班牙裔的人都非常优秀
I find European Hispanics vastly superior.
这是洛杉矶典型的维多利亚时代风格
This is a classic L.A. Victorian,
是1920年代由一位享誉盛名的医生所建
built in the 1920s by a doctor to the stars.
正如你们所见  建得精妙绝伦
As you can see, it's just fabulous.
这些蒂凡尼装饰都是真品
These are real Tiffany fixtures.
房子里的所有设施都很现代化
Everything else in the house has been updated.
加布里埃尔  等一下
Uh, Gabriel. Hold on.
抱歉  这是我儿子
Uh, I apologize for my son.
很明显  他总是带着他的滑板
Apparently he's got the skateboard
形影不离
surgically attached to his body.
他到哪儿到带着它
He doesn't go anywhere without it.
没关系  雷默斯先生
It's quite all right, Mr. Ramos.
只要别在地板上留下刮痕就行了
As long as we don't leave any marks on the floor.
还需要再等其他孩子吗
Are we waiting for another sibling?
不  就一个  谢谢
No, we just have the one. Thank you.
家具是前一任房主留下的
The furnishing is from the previous owner,
但如果你们看中哪件
but if you see anything that you like,
我想这些家具也是可以
I'm sure the estate is open to selling
适价出售的
at the right price.
这里真棒  宝贝  看看这屋子
This is amazing, babe. Look at this house.
说到钱  玛西  我也知道经济不景气
Um, speaking of money, Marcy, I know the, uh, economy is down,
但何故要价会低于市价这么多呢
but why is the asking price so far below market?
不会有霉菌或氡气的问题吧
There isn't a problem with mold or radon, is there?
不  原因再简单不过
No. Nothing so simple.
由于要公开透明化
In the interest of full disclosure,
我得告诉你们之前的屋主
I must inform you that the previous owners passed away
死在了这里
in the house.
怎么回事
Oh. How?
妻子因难产而死
The wife died during childbirth,
于是丈夫悲痛万分而自杀了
and the husband, in his grief, committed suicide.
他在二楼的天花板上自缢
He hung himself from the second-story balcony.
实在是一个悲剧浪漫爱情故事
It's a tragically romantic love story.
这是他们的狗狗  海莉
This is their dog, Hallie.
她是哈蒙一家仅剩的成员
She's the only remaining member of the Harmon family.
我收养了她
I've adopted her.
至少他们不是枉死
Well, at least they weren't murdered.
雷默斯太太
Mrs. Ramos.
带你去看别的房子也可以
I'd be happy to show you another house.
但无论搬进哪一座
But no matter where you go,
前人的痕迹  总是挥之不去
you'll be moving into somebody's history.
只不过这间屋子20万美元就可以买到
Only this one can be had for $200,000
比我上一次卖掉它的时候还便宜
less than the last time I sold it.
你觉得如何  加布
What do you think, Gabe?
我不信鬼怪
I don't believe in ghosts.
他当然会这么说了
Of course he would say that.
我们还要继续参观屋子吗
Should we continue the tour?
当然
Yes. Sure.
我想你们一定会爱上这厨房的
I know you're going to love the kitchen.
它配有大理石料理台
It's got marble countertops,
一个早餐角
a breakfast nook,
还有  你们见过煮面加水器吗
and have you ever seen a pasta arm?
-没有  -没有
- No. - No.
我也没亲眼见过  我独居
Personally, I haven't-- I live alone--
不过哈蒙太太自诩是个美食家
but Mrs. Harmon fancied herself a bit of a gourmet.
看一下后院的凉亭
Notice the gazebo in the backyard.
你没事吧
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
我  我滑倒了
I-I slipped.
妈  妈妈在哪里
Where-where's Mom?
她走进厨房的那一刻
Oh, the second she stepped foot in the kitchen,
我方就沦陷了
it was game over.
我想我们要买一间屋子了
I think we just bought ourselves a house.
来吧  你得看看这屋子的其他地方
Come on, you gotta check out the rest of this place.
肯定有地方能放张桌球台
There's definitely room for a pool table.
想象一下盛夏的时候浅酌着莫吉托鸡尾酒
Imagine sipping a nice Mojito on a hot summer day.
你们应该比我们这些美国佬要耐热吧
I guess you folks tolerate the heat better than us gringos.
我说的对吗
Am I right?
已出售
我看到又有新的一家人搬到你隔壁了
I see you've got a new family moving in next door.
没错  我注意到了
Yes, I noted that.
我真心希望他们  待人友善
Oh, I do hope they're a... nice family.
我还要亲自上门恭贺乔迁
I'd go over there and welcome them personally,
但可以想见  回到那间屋子
but as you may imagine, returning to that house
对我来说很艰难
is difficult for me.
在我目睹了那些事以后
After what I saw.
你个傻逼
You stupid son of a bitch.
拜托别告诉我你们还有坏消息
Please tell me that you're not here with any more bad news.
事实上  没有什么确切的消息
No real news, actually.
那你们还没有找到那个小宝贝吗
So you still haven't found that precious baby?
-完全没有踪影  -真是  令人担忧
- No trace. - That's very... worrying.
我们想再听你说一次事情经过
We'd like to go over your statement again.
以确保我们没有遗漏任何事
Just to make sure we didn't miss anything.
-当然  -你说你
- Of course. - You said you'd
在七点半左右到哈蒙家
gone over to the Harmons' at approximately 7:30 p.m.
探望哈蒙医生和他的女儿
to check on Dr. Harmon and his daughter.
在按了门铃却无人应门之后
After ringing the bell and getting no response,
你决定自己进去
you decided to enter the premises.
已有太多悲剧在那里发生
Being no stranger to tragedy,
所以我相当担心
I was understandably concerned.
结果证明我所猜无误
Prescient, as it turned out.
你个傻逼
You stupid son of a bitch.
我真不敢相信她杀了我
I can't believe she killed me.
你活该
Serves you right.
我直觉就想逃离那里
My first instinct was to flee.
想大叫着飞奔而出绝不回头
To run screaming and never return.
但后来我想到了那个孩子
But then I thought of the baby.
靠
Shit.
爸爸
Dad?
真是感人肺腑
Well, that's all very touching.
但孩子上哪去了
But where the hell's the baby?
于是我就去找哈蒙家的女儿
So I went searching for the Harmons' daughter.
当我发现她也已经死了
And when I discovered that she was gone, too...
我就知道到底发生了什么
I understood what must have happened.
你来看我的孩子吗
Have you come to see my baby?
我来带走我孙子
I've come to fetch my grandson.
你说带走就带走吗
Oh, you think so?
哈蒙太太站在我这边
Mrs. Harmon agrees with me.
孩子可不能在死者之屋长大
House of the dead is no place to raise a child.
这孩子就可以
It is for this baby.
-他很特别  -他是我的
- He's special. - He's mine.
除非我死
Over my dead body.
你不都已经死了吗
We're well past that.
操
Aw, shit.
瓦奥莱特抢过孩子  逃之夭夭
Violet took that child, and fled.
谁知道逃到哪里去了
God knows where.
但我每晚
But I keep them both
都不忘记为他俩祈祷
in my prayers, every night.
那么
Well...
如果  你想起瓦奥莱特说过
If you, uh, think of anything Violet said to you
任何有关她行踪的信息
that could, uh, indicate where she might have gone,
你就告诉我们
you will let us know?
一定立刻通知你们
Oh, without hesitation.
感谢你抽出时间见我们
Thank you for your time.
谁是我的宝贝小天使
Who's my good little angel, huh?
Who's my good little angel?
你就是我的宝贝小天使
Oh, there's my good little angel.
你是谁
Who are you?
你对音乐的品味可真不怎么样
You have awful taste in music.
美国德克萨斯州迷幻朋克乐队
屁眼冲浪者乐队
Butthole Surfers?
喂  你这算私闯民宅
Hello? Breaking and entering.
你是谁
Who are you?
我死后的鬼魂
A ghost of my former self.
瓦奥莱特  我住在附近
Violet. I live in the neighborhood.
你的手冷冰冰的
Your hand's cold.
俗话说得好
You know what they say.
手冷心热
Cold hands, warm heart.
美国第一支朋克乐队
-喂  -你连雷蒙斯乐队的唱片都没有吗
- Yo! - Don't you have any Ramones?
1984和1986年雷蒙斯乐队的两张专辑
比如"野性男孩"  或者"坚韧不死"
Like "Animal Boy", or "Too Tough To Die"?
喂  离开我的房间
Hey. Get out of my room.
你确定想一个人待着吗
Are you sure you want to be alone?
传闻这房子充满了游荡的孤魂
They say this house is haunted.
你神经不正常  是吧
You're kind of twisted, aren't you?
你无法想象
You don't know the half of it.
你还好吗
You okay?
还好  地板有点不正常
Yeah. This floor is warped.
你知道什么不正常吗
You know who's warped?
那个房产经纪人玛西
That realtor, Marcy.
有吗  我觉得她很性感
You think? I think she's hot.
性感火辣
Red hot.
性感撩人
Smokin' hot.
是吗
Really?
看来我得提防下那个婊子了
I may have to waste that bitch, then.
恕我没那么多体力让你俩分享
Hey. There's enough of me to go around.
我可不喜欢与人分享
Well, I'm not into sharing.
咱们今晚就给房子洗礼如何
Are we gonna christen the house tonight?
这答案你喜欢吗
Does this answer your question?
喜欢得不得了
This does.
宝贝  加布就在楼上
Babe... Gabe's upstairs.
我记得当年我们也同他俩一样
I remember when we were like that.
在一切尚未发生之前
In the beginning.
未完待续
To be continued.
-说到这里  -怎么了
- On that note. - Yes?
加布今年就毕业了
Gabe's graduating this year.
这房子又这么大
This house is so big.
你不觉得就咱倆的话有点空荡荡吗
Do you think we'll be lonely?
想要个孩子
A baby?
你不觉得我太老了吗
Don't you think I'm too old?
马上就老了  快了
Almost. Almost.
所以要把握大好时光
So we should get going.
在这房子里  我失去了两个孩子
I lost two babies in this house.
其中一个都没有呼出一口气就死了
One of them never even took a breath,
另一个被康丝坦斯偷走了
and Constance stole the other one.
至少他离开了这栋凶宅
At least he's out of this house.
他们看起来这么幸福
They seem like such a nice couple.
他们不能在这栋房子里有孩子
They can't have a baby in this house.
你说得对
You're right.
我们得采取点行动
We have to do something.
你们得伸出援手
You're going to need help.
凶宅里有些鬼魂满怀仇怨
Some spirits in the house are angry and vengeful,
一心将他们的命运报复到别人身上
and eager to inflict their fate on others.
但是大部分鬼魂是无辜  善良的冤魂
But many of us are innocent, kind, blameless victims
死于他人之手
at the hands of another.
我们不想再看到有人在这里受折磨
And we don't want to see more suffering in this house.
你梦见了什么
What were you dreaming about?
操
Shit!
我想我知道
Bet I know.
如果我能做梦的话  也会梦见她
I'd dream about her, too, if I could dream.
可我不会再做梦了
I don't think I do anymore.
见鬼  你是谁
What the hell? Who are you?
你在我房间里做什么
What are you doing in my room?
这曾经是我的房间
This used to be my room.
之后变成她的房间
And then it was hers.
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
瓦奥莱特
Violet.
她曾是我的女朋友
She was my girlfriend.
之前那个诡异的小妞
The freaky chick from before?
你这个"诡异"是什么意思
What do you mean by freaky?
她看起来挺酷的  我俩之间没什么
She seemed really cool. Nothing happened.
她没说她有男朋友了
She didn't say she had a boyfriend.
我们分手了
We kind of broke up.
这样啊
Right.
我是说
Well, I mean...
这女孩我不能染指  伙计  我懂了
It's totally hands off, dude. I get it.
不
No...
我想你不懂
I don't think you do.
该死
Shit!
妈妈
Mom?!
我的老天
Oh, my God!
米盖尔  米盖尔
Miguel! Miguel!
米盖尔
Miguel!
离我远点  离我远点
Stay away from me. Stay away from me.
滚开
Get away from me!
滚
Get away!
-呆着  别动  -你到底想干吗
- No! You stay here! - What do you want?!
加布
Gabe!
为什么
Why?!
不要
No!
为什么
Why?!
我想让她快乐
I want her to be happy.
我看得出来  她喜欢你
She liked you, I could tell.
-你是个好人吧  -什么
- You're a good guy, right? - What?
你朋友很多
I mean, you got all these friends
喜欢运动
and you played some sports.
学习也很好  对吗
You make good grades, right?
一般般
Average.
一般就是很好
Average is good.
正常很好
Normal is good.
她该有正常的生活
She deserves normal.
给我滚远点
Get out of my way!
我不想伤害你
I don't want to hurt you!
不过我的确得杀了你
Though I do have to kill you.
米盖尔
Miguel...
你该睁开双眼
it's time for you to open your eyes
看清这里的样子和对你的影响
and see what this place is, what it can do.
我要有人来感受我的痛苦
I need someone to feel my pain.
我来带路吧
Let me lead you.
看看他对我做了什么
Look what he did to me.
快跑
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this?
我告诉过你了  我们之间什么都没发生
Please, I told you, man, nothing happened!
你能不能别看着我
Could you maybe not look at me?
-什么  -你能不能...
- What? - I mean, could you...
你能不能站起来
could you, like, stand up or...
或者转过去什么的
I don't know, turn around or something?!
求你了
Please...
别杀我
don't kill me.
这不是针对你
Oh, it's nothing personal.
她那么孤单
It's just that she's all alone.
不该这样的  站起来
And that's not right! Stand up!
神父啊
Padre.
别白费力气了  快点
Stop that, stop that. Come on.
转过去
Turn around.
真调皮
Naughty boy.
史黛西会怎么想
What would Stacy think?
天啊  我在做梦呢
Oh, God, I'm dreaming.
你清醒着呢
You're wide awake.
天啊
Oh, God!
God!
米盖尔
Miguel!
史黛西
Stacy!
Stacy?
-米盖尔  -史黛西
- Miguel! - Stacy!
放开她
Leave her alone!
-本  本  -滚开
- Ben! Ben! - Get away from her.
本
Ben.
你这个变态的混蛋
You sick, perverted bastard.
他们才搬进来
They're barely moved in,
你就开始觅食了吗
you're already preying on the new meat?
你们究竟是什么人
Who the hell are you people?
他生前是我丈夫
He used to be my husband.
你们不知道  我早就想这么做了
You have no idea how long I've been wanting to do that.
You have no idea how long I've wanted to do that.
这就是你们的下场
This is what it does to you.
这栋房子
This house.
快跑
Run.
泰特  别
Tate, no.
放下刀  泰特
Put down the knife, Tate.
不行
I can't.
我是为了你
I'm doing this for you.
我没能救你
I couldn't save you.
都是我的错  才让你这么孤单
It's my fault you're alone.
我不孤单啊  我的家人都在
But I'm not alone. My family's here now.
不够
It's not enough.
你需要有人陪
You need someone.
那个人不是他
Not him.
那你想要谁
Then what do you want?!
我之前想要的是你
What I wanted was you.
你叫我走开的
You told me to go away.
但我还没能道别
But I never said good-bye.
过来  让我跟你道别吧
Come let me say good-bye.
再见了  泰特
Good-bye, Tate.
加布  加布  快点
Gabe! Gabe, come on!
快点  快点  快点
Come on, come on, come on.
又有别的倒霉蛋要搬进来了
Some other poor family's just gonna move in here.
他们根本不知道自己要住进的是什么地方
Suckers who will have no idea what they're in for.
而我们就知道该怎么做了
And we know exactly what to do.
本次旅行包括了这座天使之城
Our tour concludes with one of the most famous
最著名的凶宅
houses of horror in the City of Angels.
最近哈蒙一家的血腥惨剧
And the recent and bloody tragedy of the Harmon family...
这没有什么好看的
No, there's nothing to see here.
让这个凶宅更加的
...only adds to the infamy of
声明狼藉
the Murder House!
我还得把这个房子卖掉
I have to sell this house.
离开这
Get out of here!
已经够了
It's enough already!
这样我怎么把它卖掉
Now I have to sell this house!
你有时间吗
Have you got a minute?
我知道  我是你现在最不想看见的人
I know. I'm the last person you want to see right now.
你根本不是人
You're not a person.
你就是个怪物
You're a monster.
我很还念我们以前的治疗  本
I really miss our talks, Ben.
它们真的帮了我很多
They were really helping me.
放屁
Bullshit.
你就是个精神病  泰特
You're a psychopath, Tate.
你心理失常  心理治疗根本没用
It's a mental disorder, and therapy can't cure it.
这就是你的诊断  我是个精神病
So that's your diagnosis? I'm a psychopath?
是  而且是最糟糕的那种
Yep, and the worst kind.
你魅力非凡  惹人注目
You're charismatic and compelling
还是个病态的骗子
and a pathological liar.
不过别听我的  我也是个骗子
But don't listen to me. I'm a total fraud.
顺便说下  心理治疗根本没有用
And by the way, therapy doesn't work.
没有用  那为什么这些人要治疗
It doesn't work? Then why do people do it?
因为它们不想
Because they don't wanna
为自己的糟糕生活负一点责任
to take any responsibility for their crappy lives!
所以他们付钱让治疗师来听他们的废话
So they pay a therapist to listen to their bullshit
让这一切都变得特别
and make it all feel... special.
他们就不会责怪他们的疯老妈
So they can blame their crazy mothers
搞砸了一切
for everything that went wrong.
耳熟吗
Sound familiar?
真是个好买卖
It's a great racket, too.
一周又一周
Week after week,
一月又一月  一年又一年
month after month, year after year
我们收着钱  但心里知道那根本没用
we collect checks, but deep down we know it doesn't work.
你个婊子养的
You son of a bitch.
我们是一类人  泰特
We're not so different, Tate.
但我也是个坏人
I'm a bad person, too.
我伤害了我最应该去爱的人
I hurt the people I was supposed to... love the most.
但是她们原谅了你  对吗
But they forgave you, right?
也许瓦奥莱特也会原谅我
Maybe Violet will forgive me, too.
她不会  人们可以去原谅那些
She can't. You can only forgive someone
直接伤害自己的人
for what they've done to you directly.
那些你杀掉的人
Those people you murdered?
只有他们才可以宽恕你
They're the only ones who can forgive you,
但你没有给他们机会
and you took away their chance.
就这样吗
So this is it?
我什么都做不了了吗
There's no... there's nothing I can do?
不能获得宽恕了吗
There's no chance of mercy?
戏演得真棒  泰特
Terrific performance, Tate.
受到误解的孩子的那套把戏
The whole misunderstood kid act? Oh...
我上当了  瓦奥莱特也上当了
I fell for it, Violet did, too.
但是一个精神病  定义上来讲
But a psychopath, by definition,
是不会感到后悔的
is incapable of remorse.
所以  拜托  我们再来一次
So, come on, let's try this again
说点真的
for real this time.
你
You...
毁掉了我最在乎的一切
destroyed everything that mattered most to me.
你现在还会想从我这里得到什么
What could you possibly want from me now?
我不知道定义是怎么说的
I don't know about definitions,
但我真的很后悔  本
but I really am sorry, Ben.
对你最感到愧疚
To you more than anyone.
说抱歉很容易
Sorrys are easy.
不如对你的所作所为负起责任吧
What about taking responsibility for the things you've done?
天哪  你连那些话都说不出来
Christ, you can't even say the words.
在1994年
In 1994...
我放火烧伤我妈妈的男朋友
I set my mom's boyfriend on fire...
然后我射杀了西田高中的15个学生
...and then I shot and killed 15 kids at Westfield High.
我杀死了在你们之前
I murdered the gay couple
住在这里的那对同性恋
who lived here before you...
我还强奸了你的老婆
...and I raped your wife.
还有其他的事情
There were other things, too.
其他我伤害的人
Other people I hurt.
我会告诉你所有的事
I'll tell you everything.
我不是你的神父  泰特
I'm not your priest, Tate.
我不能赦免你任何的罪
I can't absolve you for any of this.
对  我懂
Right, I get that.
但是你能不能
But can you just...
偶尔跟我聊聊
...hang out with me sometimes?
有人吗
Hello?
谢天谢地你来了
Oh, thank God you're here.
我累坏了
I'm so exhausted.
你是新来的保姆
You're the new nanny?
谁啊
Hello?
-诺拉  -请叫我蒙哥马利太太
- Nora? - Mrs. Montgomery, please.
母亲说这是必须遵守的规矩
Mother taught me that's a rule to live by:
决不能让仆人喊我的名字
never allow the help to call you by your first name, so...
这是不是我的孩...
Is that my ba...
蒙哥马利太太  请原谅
Uh, forgive me, Mrs. Montgomery.
我本会早点儿来的  可我
I would have come sooner, but I...
我以为他没活下来  胎死腹中
I didn't think he made it; I thought he was stillborn.
差点儿
Nearly.
他哭了一声  就过世了
He made one tiny little cry and then passed on.
显然只有我见证了这一幕  查尔斯没看见
Apparently, I'm the only one who witnessed it; Charles didn't.
他真是天才
Genius.
我告诉你  这孩子闷闷不乐
He's an unhappy child, I'll tell you that.
是你啊  你是孩子的亲妈
Oh, it's you-- the birth mother.
可能是因为你怀孕时营养不良
Perhaps it was your poor nutrition
或者是遗传缺陷
or just your genetic inferiority.
反正我很不满意  这孩子病怏怏的
In any case, I'm quite dissatisfied. He's a weakling.
至少他的肺很强壮  我在楼上都能听见他的哭声
Well, his lungs are strong; I could hear him upstairs.
我能抱抱吗
May I?
不行  把手拿开
No, hands off!
你们这些人  以为可以突然出现
You people-- you think you can just show up
说你有权把亲儿子要回去  但这事早安排好了
and claim some sort of birthright, but arrangements were made.
这孩子是我的
This baby is mine.
我理解
I understand.
但我知道些办法
But I do know some... some tricks that might
可以让他安静下来
be helpful to quiet him down.
你给他起了什么名字
What do you call him?
小哭闹鬼
Little Noisy Monster.
别哭  小宝宝*
*Hush, little baby
别出声*
*Don't say a word
妈妈给你买只小鸟*
*Mama's gonna buy you a mockingbird
要是小鸟不唱歌*
*If that mockingbird don't sing
爸爸就给你买个钻戒*
*Papa's gonna buy you a diamond ring.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我原本还担心
I was actually afraid
要是他这么哭下去  我会伤害他
I might harm him if he didn't quiet down.
几天来我怎么哄他都不管用
He has been inconsolable for days and days.
折腾的我筋疲力尽
I am so exhausted.
我的天  我觉得自己需要
Oh, dear, I think I might need to...
歇会儿
take a rest.
要不你晚上帮我照顾他吧
Perhaps you could keep him for the night.
歇去吧  蒙哥马利太太  你得好好休息
You take a rest, Mrs. Montgomery. You need a nice rest.
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
我不太确定自己是否有耐心做母亲
I'm not entirely sure I have the patience to be a mother.
大概因为我换了那么多讨厌的保姆
Probably all of those hideous nannies.
但说实话  我妈也好不到哪儿去
Mother wasn't very good at it either, truth be told.
是叫你尼古拉斯好呢
Are you gonna be a Nicholas?
还是叫约拿好呢
Or a Jonah?
要不叫杰弗里吧
Or a Jeffrey?
叫你小杰弗里好吗
Are you gonna be a little Jeffrey?
你想叫什么名字呢  小宝贝
Who are you gonna be, little guy?
莫伊拉  你在干嘛呢
Moira, what are you doing?
我在用醋擦柜子呢  哈蒙太太
Scouring the cabinets with vinegar, Mrs. Harmon.
那家人搬走时
I... I just noticed how
我留意到柜子有点粘粘的
sticky they were when the new family moved out.
我也不知道自己该做什么好
I don't know what else to do with myself.
我只懂打扫  所以我接着干下去吧
Cleaning is what I'm good at, so I'll just carry on.
莫伊拉  我同情你
Sorry, Moira.
快看这是谁
Look who I found.
他原本在地下室里
He was in the basement.
他和诺拉在那下面  不停地哭
He was down there with Nora, wouldn't stop crying.
我就知道她不会带孩子
I knew she couldn't handle him.
她不是真的想要带孩子
She doesn't really want a baby.
她只是抱着这个想法不放
She just got stuck on that idea.
她就不是做母亲的料
Not a motherly bone in her body, that one.
你想抱抱他吗
Do you want to hold him?
抱稳了
Here you go.
真是个娇弱的小东西
He's such a frail little thing.
皮肤像水蜜桃一样粉嫩
His skin is like peaches.
我要不是那么风骚
I would have made a good mother,
肯定也能做个好妈妈
if I hadn't been such a little tramp.
不好意思
Forgive me.
老仆女的自怨自艾是最让人受不了的
There's nothing worse than a self-pitying old maid.
我需要人帮忙一起照顾他
You know, I'm gonna need so much help with him.
我不能接受这个职务  我不懂带孩子
I can't accept such a position. I'm not trained as a nanny.
我不是想让你为我们工作
I wasn't thinking that you would come work for us.
我是想问你  你愿不愿意做他的教母
I was gonna ask you if you wanted to be his godmother.
如果这能让你觉得安稳些
If that'd make you feel safer...
我觉得你能成为这个家庭很好的一员
I think you'd be a great addition to the family.
我在阁楼上找到了这些东西
I found these in the attic.
这些装饰品真古老
These ornaments are ancient.
确实很古老
I suppose they are.
瓦奥莱特  你会明白的
You'll come to understand, Violet,
如果你的生命停留在今天
that the word "ancient" will lose all its meaning
"古老"这个词将毫无意义
when your entire existence is one long today.
好  大家准备好了吗
Okay, everybody ready?
瞧瞧
Look at that.
我很自豪的说  是我亲自砍回来的
I chopped it down myself, I'm proud to say.
你们见过如此漂亮的东西吗
Have you ever seen anything so beautiful?
我见过
I have!
瞧瞧他  他真可爱
Look at him. He's so amazing.
性格特别好  从来不哭
Best temperament. Hardly ever cries.
真像他爸爸
Looks like his daddy.
-想抱抱他吗  -好
- Want to hold him? - Mm-hmm.
抱稳了
Here you go.
维维安  我从来没奢望过
I didn't think it was possible for me, Vivien...
但我确实很幸福
but I'm happy.
兰波  19世纪法国天才诗人  为情痴狂
别自作多情了  兰波
Grow a pair, Rimbaud.
她不在乎你
She's not into you.
她心里不会再有你的位置
You're not getting back into her.
她永远都不会再理你了
She'll never talk to you again.
我等她
I'll wait.
等到她接受为止
Forever, if I have to.
三年后
你今天想不想
How would you feel
好好露一手啊  海伦
about working a miracle today, Helen?
康丝坦斯  难得你大驾光临啊
Constance, you get your ass in my chair!
最近忙什么呢  美女
Oh, where you been, girl?
还以为你嫌弃我们家找新发廊了呢
I was starting to think you found yourself another salon.
当然不是   不  不  不
Oh, heavens no, no, no, no!
不是的   只是最近足不出户惯了
No, I've just been a bit housebound of late.
好了  可别被我摘下头巾后的样子吓到
Now, don't shriek when this scarf comes off.
伊卡璐小姐  伊卡璐染发剂形象代言  头发金黄蓬松
就快变成伊卡璐小姐了
Lady Clairol and I have become entirely too familiar.
足不出户  出什么事了吗
Housebound? You have an accident?
没有
No.
家里新添了个小孩
I had a baby.
小孩
A... A baby?
一个男孩
A boy.
一个儿子
A son!
我...不  当然不是亲生儿子
Oh, I... No, I-I didn't give birth to him, of course.
不  他是...
No, he was the, um...
我母亲这边远房表亲的小孩
child of distant cousins on my mother's side.
弗吉尼亚州的德朗普利一家
The DeLongprees of Virginia.
艾弗琳和斯蒂夫
Evaline and Steve.
他们不幸死于
They died tragically
里士满郊外高速路的一场车祸
in a highway accident outside Richmond,
那可怜的孩子从此成了孤儿
leaving that poor little angel an orphan.
真可怕
Terrible.
的确  但小迈克尔和我
Yes, but little Michael and I
命中注定有一段母子缘
were meant to be together.
他注定要成为我的儿子
He was meant to be my son.
而我  成为他的母亲
And I, his mother.
可我受够了
And I am sick
自己这一副奶奶的模样
of looking like his grandmother.
好了  看你化腐朽为神奇吧
So... here. You work your magic.
海伦
Oh, Helen!
你是个货真价实的艺术家
Oh, you truly are an artist.
艺术家也要靠好胚子
Well, even an artist needs the right materials.
康丝坦斯  我认识你这么多年了
You know, Constance, in all the years I've known you,
还从没见你如此活力四射光彩照人
I don't think you have ever looked younger or more radiant.
一点没错  是吧
It's true, isn't it?
我能说几句心里话吗
May I confide something?
自孩提时代
Ever since I was a little girl,
我就自命不凡
I knew I was destined for great things.
觉得自己将来会名扬四海
I was gonna be somebody--
成为一个...
a person of...
伟人
significance.
我曾经以为  我会成为银幕之星
A star of the silver screen, I once thought.
但...
But...
梦想照进现实时  却成了梦魇
my dreams became nightmares.
闪亮的桂冠遥不可及...
Instead of laurels...
葬礼的花圈挥之不去
funeral wreathes.
荣光暗淡
Instead of glory...
寂寞生寒
...bitter disappointment,
苦痛不减
cruel afflictions.
现在我终于明白
Well, now I understand
命运苦我心智
tragedy was preparing me...
必有大任降之
for something greater.
以前的种种不顺都是教训
Every loss that came before was a lesson.
是上天在锻炼我
I was being prepared.
而现在我终于明白目的何在
And now I know for what.
一切都为了这个孩子
This child.
一个出类拔萃的小男孩
A remarkable boy.
注定会成就非凡之事
Destined for greatness!
需要一位同样出类拔萃的母亲
In need of a remarkable mother,
一位经历挫折和逆境磨练的
someone forged in the fires of adversity...
人生导师...
...who can guide him...
来传授他智慧
...with wisdom,
赋予他坚强
with firmness,
包容他以爱
with love.
不好意思我来晚了  弗洛拉
I apologize for being so late, Flora.
都怪海伦非得和我唠叨
But Helen had to go into minute detail
她侄女的成年仪式  我都听烦了
every tiresome moment of her niece's Bat Mitzvah.
真想不到他们肯在一个13岁小孩身上
The amount of money those people
花那么多钱...
throw away on a 13-year-old is...
弗洛拉
Flora?
我该拿你怎么办啊
Now what am I gonna do with you?